critical race theory in education. It's a racist curriculum used to teach children
that somehow their white skin is not equal to black skin and other things in education.
So there's not people in here fighting for regular Americans. The guy, the average white
male trying to climb the corporate ladder when his problem is being white male.
Hoover City Schools, Birmingham, Alabama, scheduled a black author, Derek Barnes,
to read one of his children's books to their elementary schools, and then canceled him
at the last minute. Now at first they tried to claim that they were canceling him because he
failed to provide some contract materials that they had asked for. However, the superintendent,
Dee Fowler, later retracted that claim and admitted that it was due to a parent complaint.
And I got you on video that you're destroying my car. Thank you. Get the fuck out of this
neighborhood. You fucking shit. So you fucked up your car, bitch. And you think that shit
is cute, bitch. But is it, bitch? You fucking figure, you bitch.
For Black History Month, all black people should just be allowed to take a long nap
because this shit is tiring. But I'm both.